The terrifying legend of the Jersey Devil is alive.
The Barrens is a horror, thriller film directed by Darren Lynn Bousman.
A man takes his family on a camping trip and becomes convinced they are being stalked by
the legendary monster of the New Jersey Pine Barrens: the Jersey Devil.
Richard Vineyard, played by Stephen Moyer.
Cynthia Vineyard, played by Mia Kirshner.
Sadie Vineyard, played by Allie MacDonald.
Ryan, played by Erik Knudsen.
Deputy Ranger, played by Demore Barnes.
Ranger Bob, played by J. LaRose.
The Barrens is a 2012 American horror film written and directed by Darren
Lynn Bousman and starring Stephen Moyer and Mia Kirshner.
The film was released under different titles in several European territories: e.g., as Jersey Devil in the German-speaking countries, as The
Forest in Belgium and France, and as Devil in the Woods in the United Kingdom, when shown on The Horror Channel in January 2015.
The tone is dark and intense.